Uncover the corners of reality.
Corner Office is a comedy, mystery film directed by Joachim Back.
In this office satire, Orson, a straight-laced employee, retreats to a blissfully
empty corner office to get away from his lackluster colleagues.
But why does this seem to upset them so much?
Orson, played by Jon Hamm.
Rakesh, played by Danny Pudi.
Alyssa, played by Sarah Gadon.
Andrew, played by Christopher Heyerdahl.
Carol, played by Allison Riley.
Mitchell, played by Bill Marchant.
Corner Office is a 2022 American mystery-comedy drama film directed by Joachim Back and
written by Ted Kupper, based on the novel The Room by Jonas Karlsson.
The film stars Jon Hamm, Danny Pudi, Sarah Gadon and Christopher Heyerdahl.
The film premiered at the Tribeca Film Festival on June 9, 2022
and was released in theaters on August 4, 2023.
The film explores themes of hopeless, dramedy,
workplace comedy, dubious, gloomy.
The tone is lighthearted and mind_bending.